The stars laid out the show
Stars shining so bright
Watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
Dance to the mystery
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So, let the tarot move
We are Kangol
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. I don't know. It's just like I don't know
Why well because it's always been to reset the panel once in a while and there's already stuff like said
No, no Aldi was saying like the F4, you know
Alright, who's that wait
Who's I just heard someone just said
What do you mean?
Is that talking to you?
Is that your boyfriend?
I'm not talking to nobody, Saki.
Is that Ray Jean-Demon?
Someone called me a B-A-N, and then they said why I am alive.
Who is that talking to you?
That's me.
Nobody said that to you.
Who's there?
I'm not tripping.
I heard it.
Can you rewind it and listen back?
Who is that?
Okay, so I got a real question.
Is that your N-word?
No, nobody said the actual
No.
Talking to you on the phone. Who's that? Okay. Thank you. You ask something called raging. Okay. Is that raging hi raging demon?
How are you?
And oh, I'm just kidding. Thank you. I got a real question. Yes. Go ahead
Who's more gay, Sandman, for watching you in the shower or just raging for watching me in the shower?
Well, I mean, I mean, it's like, oh, so, so, just to say...
Someone watches me in the shower. Someone watches you in the shower. Who's more gay? I think I think they're equally gay
But I know I don't I don't I don't say gay. I just think people like different
They don't you have female female body. I don't know body, you know, so yeah
That's a difference
We've been a women's share like certain like the same body part certain so there's like there can be
Yeah, but psyche I have a fucking 12 inch thick. You only have a one-inch thick
Oh, I do. Oh my god. You're actually a foot long. Oh my god.
It's only one is the only one. It's one inches soft, but it really turns into two inches when
it expands. Okay. Three inches. Three inches. Three inches. Three inches. Three inches. Okay.
There's nothing female about him. Yeah. Hold on. I'm sorry. I feel like Sam is more gay because
of everything. Sam is wet. He's more gay. He's more gay. But what does it matter? But it's like
If you watch like, you know,
I think if he embraces the fact that he watched you in a song.
Yeah, but if people watch like Will Ferrell in like,
you know, what's that called?
College, the college news?
Yeah.
Will Ferrell was in like that.
Will Ferrell, he was like in some movie
where he went back to college and he's like,
he's running like, and then you can see his butt.
And everyone laughs and he's like,
you're not gay if you watch that movie.
Yeah, but he has their moment in life.
So who cares about the labels?
Can you sing a moment like this by Kelly Clarkson?
I don't know that, but like, I mean, I'm in love with you.
A moment like this, some people wait a lifetime.
I mean, I'm actually in love with Regine, and that's all.
You got her? Oh, wow.
Are you making plans to meet up?
We're gonna meet up soon.
Okay, and are you excited about that, Regine?
He's asleep. He's excited. He's excited. Yeah. Well, I wonder what's gonna happen there
I mean, it's like, you know, who's it'll be interesting
But it's kind of like, you know, there's you're too well-known panel verse people
Um
Yeah, you can't really yeah, it's kind of like there's like a romance within the panel but people met on the panel version now
It's like yeah, you met on my stuff
What am I known for those psyche? What am I known for what?
Holy and what is what is what are you milking squirting milk out of your?
No
I mean, yeah
Yeah, no, I really like you diamond thing. I think you know, you're you know, it's like you're not trying to be a representative for the whole trans community
Anybody it's a lot of pressure a lot of pressure. It's a lot of pressure for like one person
I don't care about the rest of the community. I represent myself
Yeah, and then she'll say that I mean three diamonds pretty savage. She's like she's trans
But she doesn't care about the rest of the trans people. She like
She's gonna have a uterus implanted
Get pregnant get pregnant get pregnant and then have an abortion. I mean that is the that is I'm thinking at
People cannot get over the fact that one day
Put that away, so don't stop standing up at that. I don't like that. It's inappropriate. What is that? Is that real?
It's like you're very real and one day people are gonna give get mad that like I want to
represent that anymore.
I want to pop it.
Why?
You're gonna get surgery?
Yeah, I'm getting surgery this year.
This year?
Yes.
Oh my god, but are you gonna be like how long will recovery be?
I'm gonna be recovering from one year but six months after acting in my pussy pop.
You're pussy pops. No, but isn't it like require you to put like a dildo in there every day?
Myself every fucking day three times a day and let's put a dildo up myself
It's a dick is gonna go inside me and everybody knows who's dead. Oh
Okay, well, but you can go give me four six months. You can go and you can put the dildos in you
So I'm just saying like a dick is gonna be inside me. It's only gonna be one man's dick
well
Because like that's like a lot of likes a lot of like
Yeah, I don't know
Regretted because it's like it doesn't feel like a vagina doesn't feel like I'm not ever gonna regret my surgery
That's the thing. I'm gonna be happy with my but yeah, but you have a vision of what it's gonna be like
You know what it's gonna be like, you know what it's gonna be like
It's not a deal though, it's a dilator, that device that has the artificial
vagina canal from collapsing.
It sounds kind of bad.
Backup.
Let me back up.
What's up guys? Hello? Are you are you real? Are you real? Are you real? Are you real?
He's not real. Oh wow, you're a good looking guy.
Psych, we've talked like...
Why does it matter that I'm showing my boner on stage?
It's not a boner. It's kind of an inflatable hammer.
We already showed your ass cheeks on stream, Brody.
Nice to meet P.
Hi there. Hi flirty diamond nice to meet you. Have you ever done it before me? No, this is my first time saying you showed your ass cheese
Where do you always be naked? Oh, no, I see for his boobs like three times
Calm down
Are they nice
Um, well, yeah, oh my god. Yeah, they're they're nice. You know, it's kind of like and you say, oh my god
And then show it on the screen, bro
You showed her the screen. Oh my god
Yeah, yeah
Who doesn't join the club? Come on. What do you mean? She said she said my stage is doing that pretty take that out of your pants
I'm not I don't care anymore. Stop it. Take it out of your pants. So you want to see the dick now?
Who doesn't?
Oh, I don't want to see the dick corn dog. I didn't know if that's
Again stop stop stop the way take it out take it out out
Okay, Melanie back on so you take it up psyche
You know you shine you you signing up for a diddy party really soon because of what you allow it
I'm just telling you I'm signing up for one. I'm shining up for a diddy's zitty party right now
No, I'm not sure I
Throwed you party party. I don't know
Really literally try to throw one right now. No
You were crashing out right now
No, it's just happening because it's drunk
You like what you did you like you like what you shit man keep the nail keep that
I don't like it. I don't
See how they just get caught up. I'm out of here
He did it. I'm out
You go in the stream
Why am I why am I catching shrapnel my fucking my nipples?
Why is this on me now?
I think you were lying I should don't get mad. I came here for a fucking tarot reading and this is what I'm saying.
Okay, okay, okay, let's do this tarot reading.
Three card draw, three card draw.
I'm a member.
Yes, you can have one too. Let me just get this guy. This is crazy. Thanks psych. I love you psych. You're a good man
No problem. This is crazy
Justically he was able to gain that shit
Okay, but you know what God made very many different types of people and it's a rainbow
It's like a skit. Everyone's is like a different Skittles flavor, and that's just another
Skittles flavor. Right. Black Skittles and licorice.
A bunch of, a bunch of, as well as her fruits and black licorice.
Okay, so, okay, so, okay. Oh, this is really interesting. This is really interesting. Okay.
Okay, you got the judgment card. There's hold on psych psych hold on. Yeah, let's mind meld right now. Are you ready? Okay? Okay three two one
All right, I'm ready for my reading. We are meld. Okay. We're meld it. We're meld it. Okay, so we have the judgment card
And so we see like this um, you know, this is it's they kind of like
school bell or like you know the test is over like it's like you know put down
your pencils it's kind of like the judgment is being called this it's an
end to some kind of something and it's like this is especially
Emphasized by this by the world card next and now this is 20 and this is 21 and these cards are shuffled and everything
So they just they just they came out together and so this is like this kind of like you're very you're very good at reading
So you're very good. Oh, thank you. Yeah, but yeah, so this is like and this is also like a successful completion of a cycle
She's a little bit no wait wait for my first card was judgment second time was the world
And he's a hard as a world. Yes, okay
And yes, and then your third card is the eight of wands. And so this means I don't know this one
I don't know this I can't I you you've
Draw three cards from before and you I last time I got this one too. Mm-hmm. Oh, you did the eight of ones. Yep
Yeah, okay. Yeah card. So it keeps it
It was like, you know, it's ones that are like about fire, you know, there's a fire sign and like
Fast-moving motivation and passion and so this but this is like means this something is coming in really quick
I think this information has really coming really quick or after this cycle ends like the news site
You're gonna be right into the news cycle. It's like things are gonna be happening very fast. It's or you totally
Okay, good. Yeah, good. I'll leave it there. You're really good. Oh, thank you. I appreciate you
Yeah, thank you for you know, thank you guys
Now go back to gay. Yeah, yes bring your ass on the panel Brody bring you ready bring yes, oh yes
Come on guys. You're gonna get your channel deleted. Oh, yes. Why why?
You think he's bad. Oh
Cuz the wieners and oh
Are you sure this is wiener?
Well, can I get on a panda?
I'm a panda.
Can I get on a panda?
You being a panel?
No.
A panel.
Can I get on a panda?
Yeah.
Well, let's see. I don't understand how those keep letting people up.
Why do you keep putting them backstage? That's not right.
My question is for you, Florida, why do you keep...
I just want you to stop showing your cock and you keep...
My cock's so psyche. I'm not touched right now.
Why do you keep allowing it?
I know, but it's learning time.
It's learning time. I keep telling you, stop it.
But that's my cock on me standing up. I know it's it what is that? It's I guess it's I get
Animal balloon
Is your revenge because I you got kicks
I don't know if that if that was your cock then I'd be in big trouble. It's impossible that it is
Well, everyone wants to know about it
Issue it's literally nothing
Oh, nothing. It's great. Everyone loves it. Well, you know, well,
slow down and come back later. I think come back when you
calm down and when you've taken out the props out of your
pants. Okay. Look, everyone's on your panel, bro. Everyone's
lit. Yeah. It's just gonna go down and you just gotta accept
that. Okay. What's just gonna go down here? Here we go. Hell,
yes, my boy. What up, bro? What up, kid? I was chilling, man.
What up? What up? What up, man? Welcome to the fucking
I
Was watching that she was funny
Well the floating
When you show me you take it out of your pants, and then you're not gonna form out you feel like if you give me the girl spouse on
Okay, well you're talking about out of your pants. Well for a diamond keeps my purse. I'm gonna be showing some weird. Okay
FD can we see you're gonna see your the areas
No, you're not showing it stand up all the way
Okay, she's not gonna stand up. Okay. We're playing doing it again. Come back later
Okay, she's talking about she's here. Okay, no
Well, I don't know anything. It's like probably allowed. I don't it's just yeah, it's pretty damn it
You're making everyone stick
Stop it
What
Why?
You haven't seen
Oh, I have to see it. Oh my god people come on
Like many women they come backstage and make it backstage sometimes so nothing more than you
I know there's a big I mean the bulls was like
Astronomical and she was rubbing on it. It's just I don't know
Psyche, did you know tonight was the last Black Sabbath concert ever?
Oh my god
Yes, Parkinson's he was sitting down throne. It was his last show ever tonight. Oh, that's so sad
Bring your ass up here long
It's
Because it's scary
Yes, yes, yes
You already because you're showing her nipples. You're showing her nipples backstage
That's why I was screaming
Okay, no, okay, so I've been to Auschwitz like 2001 I think and I saw it's our black brothers
I knew you I knew you until I think I could tell you that's kind of guy
Have been to like a bunch of bands and concerts
Yeah.
How long have you been on YouTube since like I opened my account, they probably may last
year and then I started posting by October last year.
You've really blown up
Yeah, but I did a lot of networking and I've also known a little bit of marketing and stuff like that
So I was able to like kind of like plan it out a little bit
I just need to like the confidence and you'll start it to do it. That was the only thing I didn't have
Do you do a lot of people fuck with you?
People fuck with me. Yeah. Well, it's like a little bit because we have so many trolling communities here
And they fuck with each other most of all and it's like, you know, just me like, you know
You know, that's not it's because I'm happy to be here and stuff like that. I don't know maybe some people
I don't care if people
So funny what's so funny?
Psych is really good
It's so funny though. Why are you laughing your perseverance? Yo, I can't like
No, I really like everybody even like the trolls like I you know, I don't I don't really mind them
I even like even like Tony who's like trying to like take that much. I don't I'm not mad anybody. I love people
I really am. I really do this because I love it. Let's see. Can Dave's dogs have
cam torn dogs? How did you end up here? Let me see. Oh, hold on. Yeah. I don't know. Yeah.
How did you find that show? Do you remember? I probably put StreamYard into YouTube
and clicked on live and found you. You know what I mean?
Oh
Please don't pull down your shirt. Please don't please don't pull on me. Please. Don't yeah, I never poor bomb do you
You're backstage during it. I saw backstage your
Okay, okay
I could have brought you up
That's what she did. She was you're showing me those so I'll be back on. Okay. It worked. It worked. Okay
Accidentally you have twice I don't think he'd like I don't like still key like I had live and you're here fucking saying that my dick
It's a porn bomb when it's not I don't care. They're like psych is in a log cow. He's not like Bill
I
Didn't go naked on here. No, you didn't but you've accidentally like try to show your boobs and then accidentally show too much a couple times
And I've had to end the stream
Okay, okay, I know you haven't but you're back. Okay, it's okay
It's okay
It's not trying to cut content.
It's funny when psych panics.
Come on.
Like, how are we standing up?
Katrina.
Brons was hot when he was a woman.
You're a woman, Brons?
You've been vagina?
Yeah, I think a little like a hippie.
He was out carrying action.
Hello, Chris.
Sikey.
Saki, how's me standing up when all I did was stand up. I didn't point bomb me. I just stood up
That shit look nasty
It was just me standing up how's that my fault all I did was stand up
It's okay. Let's let's let's let's not harp on this. Okay, so
I won't I won't just stop standing up. I asked you I just asked you to stop standing up. So just
I don't like it. I don't like would you do that? Stop it. It was stand up. I didn't do nothing.
No, you had you had something in your pants. You were you're touching my big that wasn't me putting
nothing my pants off my dick. Okay. Okay. Let's let's talk about this anymore. Okay. Hey, flirty. You
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun
Don't want to see
Stop it. Stop showing you a bitch-ass nigga bronze bird you be okay far up in the air like you don't care
But really you do be careful if you're a bitch-ass nigga
You're you're you're you're drunk insane you're rough you're rough you're rough sort of theory you're rough sort of theory
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm a bitch ass nigga, alright
Yeah, you're a bitch ass nigga bruh
I got you so far in the stuff
You're a boss bruh, she sound dumb bruh
He sound dumb as fuck right now
He's got liquor in his system
They gonna start crying and somebody come at him
You know what I mean, come at him
Demi, Demi, Demi, you can taste the way
The other guy
Nice to this fall, he decided to leave
No, but she's
This is bronzer right here
Yeah, bronzer bitch ass nigga. He left for me. I'm a bitch ass. Stop saying that. Stop saying that. Stop saying that.
What the fuck?
Right. Right.
Stop it. Stop it.
You just want alcohol, whatever it is.
That is fucking stupid.
That light ass drink you set up there drinking, man.
I don't know why I want to see that shit.
You stop showing your fucking boy chest, man.
Oh man, put them shits away, man.
I got you up in a choke. Oh, yeah, shut the fuck up. Why you keep rapping the same shit?
Yeah, hey psyche put down the link somebody said the link right there
Yo, she sound like a broken record. Yeah, bro broken record
Fuck
You know it's really funny when someone tries to learn it in word and he's not cringy as fuck when they say it
Yeah, that's just so crazy
It's like why you trying to be down?
Fuck
You don't even know how to handle that base what?
Yeah, you're a babe. Yeah, this shit is crazy work. Yo, you're a rapper. I'm too relaxed of what I argue. Yo, this shit is crazy work.
I'm laughing at that. It's crazy work, yo.
Oh, yeah, you crazy work my nigga because you don't know how to handle the heat
You'd be so far up in the kitchen. You thought you're burning something, but really you fucking
Blame me enough on the bitch
This is crazy
Fucking
Corn dog yo Mojo Joe's you ever received a free membership. Okay. Thank you
Yeah
I saw you bronzer. I saw you in ass. Yo, she drunk
It seems like furry diving is just horny as fuck tonight, you know
Seriously, he's doing all this shit at the ZD party, G
No
In a strip tease like what is going on?
This is crazy. No people in the back. She won't pull him on you
And this is crazy work, you know, that's facts
Thank you. Yeah, you're a little bit you're a little bit too flirty tonight.
You're a little too flirty. They're talking about I fucking have bussy and shit.
Yo, she look like a clown. She doing that shit.
What the fuck is going on? What the fuck?
It's like he wants to zitty party.
Well, I went, you know, I went with Chris K and like, not with Aldi,
but I think he was like almost, he almost said yes.
Um, he's here. I don't think he's interested
Clarity I see you can just hang out backstage. You there's a green room. It's a snacks back there. Okay, hold on
Hello
Hey, so I was going on it's Chris. Yes, sir. Hey, old Chris cap, sir
But uh, what up, Chris?
What's going on? Are you chilling chilling?
Yes, like what up, bro
Yo, yo, John's bird. What's going on? My yo face to you, bro
Yes, sir. We all side. We all side
Yo, you know what? You know, it's crazy. I don't I don't like to mention it, but you know, it just seems like
TPP is dead and then it's just like holding a rank. So it was somewhere else. You know what I'm saying? Oh
Fuck TPP, sorry
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.